oxfordenglishtesting.com 2017-07-25

# Oxford Online Placement Test | Exam Practice Tests for KET, PET, FCE, CAE, IELTS, TOEIC, TOEFL iBT

## Privacy Policy for Oxford English Testing

This privacy policy is specific to the Oxford English Testing web site and in the event of any conflict arising overrides any other privacy policy appearing on Oxford University Press ("OUP") web sites.

**Privacy Policy**

Oxford University Press is committed to protecting your privacy online. Our policy explains how we will do this. We will review this policy in the light of comments we receive so please check the latest version. If you have any questions, please contact us.

By using the Oxford English Testing website, you are accepting the practices described in this statement.

**What information do we collect?**

When you register to the website we may ask for your name, email address, postal address, and other relevant personal information. Personal information submitted in this way is added to our access control database, hosted by a third party hosting company, and to our customer database at OUP premises. This information will be updated if you inform us of any changes.

If you have indicated your consent, we may use information in our customer databases to send you information about us and our products which we think may be of interest to you, either electronically or otherwise. Your personal information will also be used to enable us to verify you are a registered user and to deliver the Oxford English Testing resource to you.

We request personal information (such as your name, e-mail address and other contact details) from you when you contact us with registered user management queries, technical problems, to comment on the Oxford English Testing resource, or when you ask for information about how to use the service. Personal information submitted by you via a “contact us” or Support programme will not be added to our customer database and we request it simply so that we can respond to you about your query. Statistics regarding the types of queries submitted to us via a “contact us” or Support programme may be collated by us in aggregate form so that we can effectively monitor the site and improve levels of service.

We need to store information about current registered users and your use of the Oxford English Testing website in order to fulfil our contractual requirements to you and in order to deliver the Oxford English Testing resource to you. 

You may notify us either in writing or by telephone, fax or e-mail that you object to being contacted in a particular stated way. If you use more than one e-mail address to communicate with us, please notify us of each e-mail account you use.

We will only keep personal information for so long as is required to perform our obligations to you after which time we shall delete and destroy it. 

**When do we share information?**

We do not sell your personal information to others. 

We share your personal information within OUP and with Oxford Publishing Limited. We will also share your personal information with third party suppliers for the purpose of enabling such suppliers' software that we use to support your use of the Oxford English Testing website. 

The Oxford English Testing web site has been developed by and hosted by third parties but we have agreed with those third parties that they will keep your information secure and not use it for other purposes. 

If we believe that your use of the web site is unlawful or damaging to others, we reserve the right to disclose the information we have obtained through the site about you to the extent that it is reasonably necessary in our opinion to prevent, remedy or take action in relation to such conduct.

Where schools have agreed to form a chain, the schools and their authorised users (teachers and students) should be aware that a school in the chain will have the right (for proper purposes related to the management of their English testing resources) to view, process and amend the personal data in OUP’s learning management system relating to authorised users belonging to its school and any schools lower down that chain of schools.   

**Use of cookies**

Cookies are small files that we create to store information on your computer.

  * we do not use cookies to track what other sites you have visited.
  * we do not look at or track any personal or confidential information about you other than is strictly necessary for the purposes of your use of the Oxford English Testing resources.
  * we do make use of cookies to enable authorization control for online products.

**Security**

Your personal information is stored at a data centre controlled by our third party hosting company and on the customer databases at OUP. The data centre controlled by our third party hosting company is specifically designed to be physically secure and to admit authorized personnel only, who are contractually bound to keep all of our data confidential. 

Access to our customer databases at OUP is only given to those of our employees who need such access in order to carry out necessary processing of your account. 

All personal information submitted by you and entered by OUP into the Oxford English Testing resource access control system is encoded using 128-bit SSL encryption before being sent over the Internet.
